RG 003, New London County, County Court Files
Connecticut State Library
- Files, 1691-1855
  - 1745
    - November, no docket (Dom. Rex-Woodbridge) (Box 81, Folder 1-4)
  - 1746 (Box 81)
    - February, no. 2-100 (Box 81, Folder 5-8)
    - February, no docket (Abell-Williams) (Box 81, Folder 9-13)
    - June, no. 2-129 (Box 81, Folder 14-20)
    - June, no. 130-156 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - June, no docket (Armstrong-Woodbridge) (Box 82, Folder 2-7)
    - November, no. 1-119 (Box 82, Folder 8-14)
    - November, no docket (Avery-Wentworth) (Box 82, Folder 15-18)
  - 1747 (Box 82)
    - February, no. 3-57 (Box 82, Folder 19-21)
    - February, no. 58-66 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - February, no docket (Andres-Williams) (Box 83, Folder 2-4)
    - June, no. 1-107 (Box 83, Folder 5-12)
    - June, no docket (Almy-Woodbridge) (Box 83, Folder 13-18)
    - November, no. 1-32 (Box 83, Folder 19-20)
    - November, no. 33-101 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no docket (Armstrong-Wheeler) (Box 84, Folder 5-12)
  - 1748 (Box 84)
    - February, no. 1-64 (Box 84, Folder 11-15)
    - February, no docket (Abell-Woodbridge) (Box 84, Folder 16-19)
    - June, no. 1-52 (Box 84, Folder 20-21)
    - June, no. 53-130 (Box 85, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Williams) (Box 85, Folder 5-9)
    - August, no. 2-72 (Box 85, Folder 10-14)
    - August, no docket (Barstow-Wood) (Box 85, Folder 15-17)
    - November, no. 3-37 (Box 85, Folder 18-20)
    - November, no. 40-79 (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Wright) (Box 86, Folder 4-8)
  - 1749 (Box 86)
    - February, no. 1-46 (Box 86, Folder 9-12)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Wickwire) (Box 86, Folder 13-15)
    - June, no. 3-95 (Box 86, Folder 16-21)
    - June, no. 97-127 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no docket (Backus-Winchester) (Box 87, Folder 3-7)
    - November, no. 1-149 (Box 87, Folder 8-17)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Mayhem) (Box 87, Folder 18-21)
    - November, no docket (Merrill-Yeomans) (Box 88, Folder 1-3)
  - 1750 (Box 88)
    - February, no. 1-133 (Box 88, Folder 4-12)
    - February, no docket (Allyn-Yeomans) (Box 88, Folder 13-18)
    - June, no. 1-44 (Box 88, Folder 19-21)
    - June, no. 46-160 (Box 89, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no docket (Allen-Williams) (Box 89, Folder 8-14)
    - November, no. 1-88 (Box 89, Folder 15-20)
    - November, no. 89-151 (Box 90, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no docket (Adgate-Wickwire) (Box 90, Folder 5-10)
  - 1751 (Box 90)
    - February, no. 3-84 (Box 90, Folder 11-16)
    - February, no docket (Arnold-Winchester) (Box 90, Folder 18-22)
    - June, no. 1-152 (Box 91, Folder 1-9)
    - June, no docket (Allen-Dow, Roy) (Box 91, Folder 10-16)
    - November, no. 1-81 (Box 91, Folder 17-21)
    - November, no. 82-189 (Box 92, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Woodbridge) (Box 92, Folder 8-15)
  - 1752 (Box 92)
    - February, no. 1-105 (Box 92, Folder 16-21)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Woodbridge) (Box 93, Folder 1-8)
    - June, no. 1-231 (Box 93, Folder 9-20)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Yarington) (Box 94, Folder 1-8)
    - August, no. 1-112 (Box 94, Folder 9-16)
    - August, no docket (Adams-Worthylake) (Box 94, Folder 17-21)
    - November, no. 2-195 (Box 95, Folder 1-10)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Young) (Box 95, Folder 11-17)
  - 1753 (Box 95)
    - February, no. 1-29 (Box 95, Folder 18-20)
    - February, no. 40-158 (Box 96, Folder 1-7)
    - February, no docket (Allyn-Yeomans) (Box 96, Folder 5-12)
    - June, no. 1-97 (Box 96, Folder 5-12)
    - June, no. 104-188 (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no docket (Allyn-Yeomans) (Box 97, Folder 5-12)
    - July, no. 2-62 (Box 97, Folder 13-16)
    - July, no docket (Avery-Wait) (Box 97, Folder 17-18)
    - November, no. 3-55 (Box 97, Folder 19-21)
    - November, no. 56-192 (Box 98, Folder 1-6)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Williams) (Box 98, Folder 7-14)
  - 1754 (Box 98)
    - February, no. 2-111 (Box 98, Folder 15-19)
    - February, adjourned, no. 5-18 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - February, adjourned, no. 19-45 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Woodbridge) (Box 99, Folder 2-7)
    - April, no. 3-41 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - June, no. 6-182 (Box 99, Folder 9-19)
    - June, no docket (Adams-Coit) (Box 99, Folder 20-21)
    - June, no docket (Davison-Woods) (Box 100, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no. 2-221 (Box 100, Folder 8-19)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Gardiner) (Box 100, Folder 20-21)
    - November, no docket (Grent-Wickwire) (Box 101, Folder 1-4)
  - 1755 (Box 101)
    - February, no. 3-152 (Box 101, Folder 5-12)
    - February, no docket (Abell-Tracy) (Box 101, Folder 14-21)
    - February, no docket (Treasurer-Woodbridge) (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - June, no. 3-194 (Box 102, Folder 2-14)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Rogers) (Box 102, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no docket (Roland-Woodworth) (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
    - November, no. 2-179 (Box 103, Folder 3-11)
    - November, no docket (Allyn-Wright) (Box 103, Folder 12-17)
  - 1756 (Box 103)
    - February, no. 1-53 (Box 103, Folder 18-20)
    - February, no. 55-123 (Box 104, Folder 1-4)
    - February, no docket (Alger-Wood) (Box 104, Folder 5-10)
    - June, no. 1-175 (Box 104, Folder 11-19)
    - June, no docket (Alden-Chesebrough) (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - June, no docket (Clark-Williams) (Box 105, Folder 1-6)
    - November, no. 2-174 (Box 105, Folder 7-15)
    - November, no docket (Ames-Robertson) (Box 105, Folder 16-20)
    - November, no docket (Rogers-Yeomans) (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
  - 1757 (Box 106)
    - February, no. 5-112 (Box 106, Folder 3-7)
    - February, no docket (Allyn-Wood) (Box 106, Folder 8-12)
    - June, no.15-120 (Box 106, Folder 13-20)
    - June, no. 121-200 (Box 107, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no docket (Abell-York) (Box 107, Folder 6-13)
    - November, no. 2-139 (Box 107, Folder 14-21)
    - November, no. 139-167 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Waller) (Box 108, Folder 3-8)
  - 1758 (Box 108)
    - February, no. 2-106 (Box 108, Folder 9-14)
    - February, no docket (Abel-Yeomans) (Box 108, Folder 15-20)
    - June, no. 2-151 (Box 109, Folder 1-11)
    - June, no docket (Allen-Woodward) (Box 109, Folder 12-18)
    - November, no. 2-26 (Box 109, Folder 19-20)
    - November, no. 27-112 (Box 110, Folder 1-6)
    - November, no docket (Andrews-Williams) (Box 110, Folder 7-12)
  - 1759 (Box 110)
    - February, no. 2-131 (Box 110, Folder 13-18)
    - February, no docket (Acley-Lothrop) (Box 110, Folder 19-22)
    - February, no docket (Lowden-Williams) (Box 111, Folder 1-3)
    - June, no. 8-187 (Box 111, Folder 4-13)
    - June, no docket (Adams-Wright) (Box 111, Folder 14-21)
    - November, no. 4-179 (Box 112, Folder 1-13)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Williams) (Box 112, Folder 14-22)
  - 1760
    - February, no. 4-134 (Box 113, Folder 1-7)
    - February, no docket (Appleton-Woodworth) (Box 113, Folder 8-14)
    - June, no. 2-106 (Box 113, Folder 15-22)
    - June, no. 108-242 (Box 114, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no docket (Austin-Worden) (Box 114, Folder 8-17)
    - November, no. 1-109 (Box 114, Folder 18-22)
    - November, no. 110-231 (Box 115, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Worden) (Box 115, Folder 8-15)
  - 1761 (Box 115)
    - February, no. 1-126 (Box 115, Folder 16-22)
    - February, no. 128-223 (Box 116, Folder 1-5)
    - February, no docket (Abell-Woodward) (Box 116, Folder 6-13)
    - June, no. 1-193 (Box 116, Folder 14-21)
    - June, no. 194-449 (Box 117, Folder 1-14)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Minor) (Box 117, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no docket (Moor-Wright) (Box 118, Folder 1-5)
    - November, no. 2-292 (Box 118, Folder 6-20)
    - November, no. 293-502 (Box 119, Folder 1-10)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Stewart) (Box 119, Folder 11-21)
    - November, no docket (Stodder-York) (Box 120, Folder 1-2)
  - 1762 (Box 120)
    - February, no. 2-345 (Box 120, Folder 3-20)
    - February, no. 346-382 (Box 121, Folder 1-2)
    - February, no docket (Abel-Wright) (Box 121, Folder 3-13)
    - June, no. 1-139 (Box 121, Folder 14-21)
    - June, no. 140-530 (Box 122, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 531-586 (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
    - June, no docket (Adsit-Wood) (Box 123, Folder 4-18)
    - November, no. 3-79 (Box 123, Folder 19-21)
    - November, no. 80-460 (Box 124, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 461-500 (Box 125, Folder 1-3)
    - November, no docket (Box 125, Folder 4-13)
  - 1763 (Box 125)
    - February, no. 1-116 (Box 125, Folder 14-20)
    - February, no. 117-328 (Box 126, Folder 1-12)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Skinner) (Box 126, Folder 13-21)
    - February, no docket (Smith-Dom Rex) (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no. 1-338 (Box 127, Folder 3-20)
    - June, no. 339-539 (Box 128, Folder 1-13)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Jeffrey) (Box 128, Folder 14-20)
    - June, no docket (Kelcy-York) (Box 129, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no. 1-246 (Box 129, Folder 8-20)
    - November, no. 247-427 (Box 130, Folder 1-8)
    - November, no docket (Abott-Wright) (Box 130, Folder 9-18)
  - 1764 (Box 130)
    - February, no. 1-72 (Box 130, Folder 19-21)
    - February, no. 61-352 (Box 131, Folder 1-15)
    - February, no docket (Allyn-Lord, Elisha) (Box 131, Folder 16-20)
    - February, no docket (Lord, Hezekiah-Williams) (Box 132, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no. 5-293 (Box 132, Folder 6-21)
    - June, no. 294-432 (Box 133, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no docket (Allen-York) (Box 133, Folder 8-21)
    - November, no. 10-400 (Box 134, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 401-423 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - November, no docket (Abell-York) (Box 135, Folder 2-12)
  - 1765 (Box 135)
    - February, no. 1-151 (Box 135, Folder 13-21)
    - February, no. 155-337 (Box 136, Folder 1-11)
    - February, no docket (Andrus-Smith) (Box 136, Folder 12-20)
    - February, no docket (Standish-Woodward) (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no. 1-378 (Box 137, Folder 3-21)
    - June, no. 380-451 (Box 138, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no docket (Box 138, Folder 6-19)
    - September (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - November (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - 1766 (Box 138)
    - April (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - June, no. 1-303 (Box 139, Folder 1-21)
    - June, no. 304-465 (Box 140, Folder 1-13)
    - June, no docket (Adgate-Lothrop) (Box 140, Folder 14-21)
    - June, no docket (Mason-York) (Box 141, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no. 1-280 (Box 141, Folder 8-21)
    - November, no. 281-409 (Box 142, Folder 1-8)
    - November, no docket (Box 142, Folder 9-20)
  - 1767
    - February, no. 1-212 (Box 143, Folder 1-11)
    - February, no docket (Box 143, Folder 12-17)
    - June, no. 1-60 (Box 143, Folder 18-21)
    - June, no. 61-364 (Box 144, Folder 1-18)
    - June, no docket (Allin-Emerson) (Box 144, Folder 19-21)
    - June, no docket (Fillmore-Worthington) (Box 145, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no. 4-267 (Box 145, Folder 8-21)
    - November, no. 268-279 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - November, no docket (Allyn-Young) (Box 146, Folder 2-10)
  - (Box 146)
    - February, no. 6-168 (Box 146, Folder 11-21)
    - February, no. 169-193 (Box 147, Folder 1-2)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Wood) (Box 147, Folder 3-10)
    - June, no. 3-201 (Box 147, Folder 11-21)
    - June, no. 203-292 (Box 148, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no docket (Andrus-Young) (Box 148, Folder 6-14)
    - November, no. 2-100 (Box 148, Folder 15-21)
    - November, no. 101-253 (Box 149, Folder 1-9)
    - November, no docket (Abel-Williams) (Box 149, Folder 10-19)
  - 1769 (Box 149)
    - February (Adams-Belden) (Box 149, Folder 20-21)
    - February (Bellows-York) (Box 150, Folder 1-16)
    - June (Anesley-Christophers) (Box 150, Folder 17-21)
    - June (Clark-York) (Box 151)
    - November (Allyn-Whipple) (Box 152)
    - November (Whiting-Worthington) (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - 1770 (Box 153)
    - February (Abell-Woodward) (Box 153, Folder 2-17)
    - June (Adams-Brewster, Jonathan) (Box 153, Folder 18-20)
    - June (Brewster, Joseph-Shaw) (Box 154)
    - June (Sheffield-Whittelsey) (Box 155, Folder 1-6)
    - November (Atkins-Punderson) (Box 155, Folder 7-20)
    - November (Ransom-York) (Box 156, Folder 1-4)
  - 1771 (Box 156)
    - February (Adams-Worden) (Box 156, Folder 5-20)
    - June (Alger-Morgan) (Box 157)
    - June (Morse-York) (Box 158, Folder 1-10)
    - November (Abell-Hubbard) (Box 158, Folder 11-20)
    - November (Huntington-Yerrington) (Box 159, Folder 1-15)
  - 1772 (Box 159)
    - February (Adams-Ely) (Box 159, Folder 16-20)
    - February (Fanning-Woodworth) (Box 160, Folder 1-9)
    - June (Adams-Furbush) (Box 160, Folder 10-20)
    - June (Gardner-Wetmore) (Box 161)
    - June (Wheat-Yerrington) (Box 162, Folder 1-3)
    - November (Adams-Morgan) (Box 162, Folder 4-20)
    - November (Mott-Woodbridge) (Box 163, Folder 1-10)
  - 1773 (Box 163)
    - February (Andrus-Lay) (Box 163, Folder 11-20)
    - February (Leach-Woodbridge) (Box 164, Folder 1-8)
    - June (Adams-Gardiner) (Box 164, Folder 9-20)
    - June (Geer-Yarington) (Box 165, Folder 1-18)
    - November (Adams-Budington) (Box 165, Folder 19-21)
    - November (Bulkley-Wright) (Box 166)
  - 1774
    - February (Abell-Witter) (Box 167, Folder 1-16)
    - June (Adams-Darrow) (Box 167, Folder 17-21)
    - June (Dart-Truman) (Box 168)
    - June (Trumbull-York) (Box 169, Folder 1-4)
    - November (Adams-Noyes) (Box 169, Folder 5-19)
    - November (Page-Wright) (Box 170)
  - 1781
    - November, no. 1-302 (Box 171, Folder 1-14)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Governor and Company) (Box 171, Folder 15-20)
    - November, no docket (Governor and Company-Young) (Box 172, Folder 1-10)
  - 1782 (Box 172)
    - February, no. 1-148 (Box 172, Folder 11-23)
    - February, no. 150-256 (Box 173, Folder 1-8)
    - February, no docket (Andrus-Youngs) (Box 173, Folder 9-22)
    - June, no. 1-331 (Box 174, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 332-365 (Box 175, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no docket (Ames-Wright) (Box 175, Folder 3-14)
    - November, no. 2-187 (Box 175, Folder 15-21)
    - November, no. 188-365 (Box 176, Folder 1-8)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Wright) (Box 176, Folder 9-18)
  - 1783 (Box 176)
    - February, no. 1-57 (Box 176, Folder 19-21)
    - February, no. 59-512 (Box 177, Folder 1-17)
    - February, no docket (Abell-Buel) (Box 177, Folder 18-19)
    - February, no docket (Butler-York) (Box 178, Folder 1-11)
    - June, no. 1-121 (Box 178, Folder 12-20)
    - June, no. 122-399 (Box 179, Folder 1-22)
    - June, no. 402-616 (Box 180, Folder 1-18)
    - June, no docket (Allen-Woodbridge) (Box 181, Folder 1-22)
    - November, no. 2-28 (Box 181, Folder 23-24)
    - November, no. 32-369 (Box 182, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 370-688 (Box 183, Folder 1-24)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Button) (Box 183, Folder 25-26)
    - November, no docket (Capron-Yarrington) (Box 184, Folder 1-13)
  - 1784 (Box 184)
    - February, no. 1-84 (Box 184, Folder 14-21)
    - February, no. 85-417 (Box 185, Folder 1-21)
    - February, no. 418-463 (Box 186, Folder 1-4)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Woodbridge) (Box 186, Folder 5-14)
    - June, no. 3-123 (Box 186, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no. 124-463 (Box 187, Folder 1-21)
    - June, no. 465-540 (Box 188, Folder 5-18)
    - June, no docket (Abbott-Young) (Box 188, Folder 5-18)
    - November, no. 1-375 (Box 189, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 376-444 (Box 190, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no docket (Ashcraft-York) (Box 190, Folder 5-15)
  - 1785 (Box 190)
    - February, no. 3-92 (Box 190, Folder 16-20)
    - February, no. 93-304 (Box 191, Folder 1-13)
    - February, no docket (Abell-York) (Box 191, Folder 14-20)
    - June, no 1-335 (Box 192, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 336-473 (Box 193, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no docket (Abbot-York) (Box 193, Folder 8-17)
    - Novmeber, no. 3-11 (Box 193, Folder 18-19)
    - November, no. 12-374 (Box 194, Folder 1-18)
    - November, no. 379-489 (Box 195, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no docket (Adams-York) (Box 195, Folder 5-13)
  - 1786 (Box 195)
    - February, no. 1-56 (Box 195, Folder 14-17)
    - February, no. 57-332 (Box 196, Folder 1-20)
    - February, no docket (Allyn-Woodbridge) (Box 197, Folder 1-11)
    - June, no. 1-98 (Box 197, Folder 12-20)
    - June, no. 105-386 (Box 198, Folder 1-18)
    - June, no. 387-454 (Box 199, Folder 1-3)
    - June, no docket (Abbe-York) (Box 199, Folder 4-12)
    - November, no. 5-204 (Box 199, Folder 13-19)
    - November, no. 205-484 (Box 200, Folder 1-11)
    - November, no docket (Ames-Wright) (Box 200, Folder 12-21)
  - 1787
    - February, no. 1-199 (Box 201, Folder 1-20)
    - February, no. 190-352 (Box 202, Folder 1-13)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Woodward) (Box 202, Folder 14-21)
    - June, no. 1-291 (Box 203, Folder 1-21)
    - June, no. 292-435 (Box 204, Folder 1-9)
    - June, no docket (Adams-York) (Box 204, Folder 10-19)
    - November, no. 14-44 (Box 204, Folder 20-22)
    - November, no. 48-323 (Box 205, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no docket (Amory-Worthington) (Box 206, Folder 1-11)
  - (Box 206)
    - February, no. 1-163 (Box 206, Folder 12-21)
    - February, no. 164-288 (Box 207, Folder 1-9)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Worthington) (Box 207, Folder 10-21)
    - June, no. 1-246 (Box 208, Folder 1-22)
    - June, no. 247-410 (Box 209, Folder 1-17)
    - June, no docket (Alexander-Gibbs) (Box 209, Folder 18-21)
    - June, no docket (Gillet-Worthington) (Box 201, Folder 1-8)
    - December, no. 2-150 (Box 210, Folder 9-20)
    - December, no. 151-340 (Box 211, Folder 1-21)
    - December, no. 342-354 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - December, no docket (Avery-Wright) (Box 212, Folder 2-11)
  - 1789 (Box 212)
    - April (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - February, no. 1-98 (Box 212, Folder 13-21)
    - February, no. 99-179 (Box 213, Folder 1-8)
    - February, no docket (Allen-Worthington) (Box 213, Folder 9-14)
    - June, no. 1-57 (Box 213, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no. 59-242 (Box 214, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 243-339 (Box 215, Folder 1-8)
    - June, no docket (Adams-Worthington) (Box 215, Folder 9-19)
    - December, no. 1-31 (Box 215, Folder 20-21)
    - December, no. 35-301 (Box 216, Folder 1-21)
    - December, no. 303-341 (Box 217, Folder 1-4)
    - December, no docket (Aldridge-Worthington) (Box 217, Folder 5-13)
  - 1790 (Box 217)
    - February, no. 1-72 (Box 217, Folder 14-20)
    - February, no. 76-198 (Box 218, Folder 1-14)
    - February, no docket (Babcock-Woodbridge) (Box 218, Folder 15-20)
    - June, no. 1-224 (Box 219, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 225-298 (Box 220, Folder 1-6)
    - June, no docket (Alexander-Woodbridge) (Box 220, Folder 7-13)
    - November, no. 2-166 (Box 220, Folder 14-22)
    - November, no. 167-240 (Box 221, Folder 1-6)
    - November, no docket (Allyn-York) (Box 221, Folder 7-11)
  - 1791 (Box 221)
    - February, no. 7-135 (Box 221, Folder 12-20)
    - February, no. 136-155 (Box 222, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no. 1-197 (Box 222, Folder 7-20)
    - June, no. 199-252 (Box 223, Folder 1-3)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Worthington) (Box 223, Folder 4-10)
    - November, no. 1-112 (Box 223, Folder 11-20)
    - November, no. 113-187 (Box 224, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no docket (Babcock-Wright) (Box 224, Folder 8-12)
  - 1792 (Box 224)
    - February, no. 1-98 (Box 224, Folder 13-20)
    - February, no. 99-128 (Box 225, Folder 1-2)
    - February, no docket (Armstrong-Worthington) (Box 225, Folder 3-6)
    - June, no. 3-174 (Box 225, Folder 7-20)
    - June, no. 175-264 (Box 226, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no docket (Allen-Wright) (Box 226, Folder 6-14)
    - December, no. 2-135 (Box 226, Folder 15-21)
    - December, no. 137-194 (Box 227, Folder 1-5)
    - December, no docket (Beebe-Wright) (Box 227, Folder 6-10)
  - 1793 (Box 227)
    - February, no. 2-127 (Box 227, Folder 11-17)
    - February, no docket (Babcock-Williams) (Box 227, Folder 18-20)
    - June, no. 5-189 (Box 228, Folder 1-15)
    - June, no docket (Allyn-Root) (Box 228, Folder 16-20)
    - June, no docket (Rost-York) (Box 229, Folder 1-3)
    - November, no. 2-146 (Box 229, Folder 4-13)
    - November, no docket (Beckwith-Woodbridge) (Box 229, Folder 14-17)
  - 1794 (Box 229)
    - February, no. 3-56 (Box 229, Folder 18-21)
    - February, no. 57-118 (Box 230, Folder 1-5)
    - February, no docket (Alsop-Wright) (Box 230, Folder 6-10)
    - June, no. 2-155 (Box 230, Folder 11-20)
    - June, no. 157-195 (Box 231, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no docket (Adams-Wright) (Box 231, Folder 3-7)
    - November, no. 1-168 (Box 231, Folder 8-20)
    - November, no. 169-188 (Box 232, Folder 1-2)
    - November, no docket (Austin-Woodbridge) (Box 232, Folder 3-7)
  - 1795 (Box 232)
    - February, no. 4-153 (Box 232, Folder 8-17)
    - February, no docket (Backus-York) (Box 232, Folder 18-20)
    - June, no. 1-159 (Box 223, Folder 1-13)
    - November, no. 1-129 (Box 234, Folder 1-8)
    - November, no docket (Adams-Worthington) (Box 234, Folder 9-12)
  - 1796 (Box 234)
    - February, no. 1-85 (Box 234, Folder 13-18)
    - February, no docket (Ayers-Worthington) (Box 234, Folder 19-20)
    - April, no. 2-9 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - June, no. 2-205 (Box 235, Folder 2-15)
    - June, no docket (Arnold-Wylie) (Box 235, Folder 16-20)
    - November, no. 1-156 (Box 236, Folder 1-11)
    - November, no docket (Arthur-Woodworth) (Box 236, Folder 12-15)
  - 1797 (Box 236)
    - February, no. 2-108 (Box 236, Folder 16-20)
    - February, no. 112-189 (Box 237, Folder 1-4)
    - February, no docket (Abel-Woodward) (Box 237, Folder 5-9)
    - June, no. 1-118 (Box 237, Folder 10-20)
    - June, no. 119-343 (Box 238, Folder 1-15)
    - June, no docket (Armstrong-Moore) (Box 238, Folder 16-20)
    - June, no docket (Moore-Young) (Box 239, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no. 4-216 (Box 239, Folder 5-20)
    - November, no. 217-288 (Box 240, Folder 1-5)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Young) (Box 240, Folder 6-12)
  - 1798 (Box 240)
    - February, no. 1-106 (Box 240, Folder 13-20)
    - February, no. 107-162 (Box 241, Folder 1-5)
    - February, no docket (Allyn-Williams) (Box 241, Folder 6-9)
    - June, no. 2-123 (Box 241, Folder 10-20)
    - June, no. 124-255 (Box 242, Folder 1-12)
    - June, no docket (Allyn-Whiting) (Box 242, Folder 13-19)
    - December, no. 6-43 (Box 242, Folder 20-21)
    - December, no. 47-245 (Box 243, Folder 1-14)
    - December, no docket (Armstrong-Williams) (Box 243, Folder 15-20)
  - 1799
    - February, no. 1-167 (Box 244, Folder 1-13)
    - February, no docket (Avery-Wilson) (Box 244, Folder 14-17)
    - June, no. 2-31 (Box 244, Folder 18-20)
    - June, no docket (Adams-Clark) (Box 245, Folder 19-20)
    - June, no docket (Clark-Yerrington) (Box 246, Folder 1-6)
    - December, no. 4-249 (Box 246, Folder 7-20)
    - December, no. 250-329 (Box 247, Folder 1-5)
    - December, no docket (Adams-York) (Box 247, Folder 6-13)
  - 1800 (Box 247)
    - February, no. 2-115 (Box 247, Folder 14-19)
    - February, no. 116-228 (Box 248, Folder 1-9)
    - February, no docket (Armstrong-Williams) (Box 248, Folder 10-16)
    - June, no. 1-51 (Box 248, Folder 17-21)
    - June, no. 52-309 (Box 249, Folder 1-22)
    - June, no docket (Allen-Brown) (Box 249, Folder 23-24)
    - June, no docket (Browne-Wyoggs) (Box 250, Folder 1-9)
    - December, no. 2-243 (Box 250, Folder 10-26)
    - December, no. 244-350 (Box 251, Folder 1-6)
    - December, no docket (Averill-Williams) (Box 251, Folder 7-15)
  - 1801 (Box 251)
    - February, no. 4-101 (Box 251, Folder 16-24)
    - February, no. 103-250 (Box 252, Folder 1-13)
    - February, no docket (Abell-Williams) (Box 252, Folder 14-24)
    - June, no. 1-27 (Box 252, Folder 25-27)
    - June, no. 28-311 (Box 253, Folder 1-29)
    - June, no. 312-381 (Box 254, Folder 1-6)
    - June, no docket (Abell-Worthington) (Box 254, Folder 7-19)
    - December, no. 1-97 (Box 254, Folder 20-30)
    - December, no. 98-350 (Box 255, Folder 1-23)